gomerch.com 2013-08-05

# Privacy Policy | Go Merch

Privacy Policy:

Effective on January 4, 2010

This privacy statement describes how GoMerch collects and uses the personal information you provide on our Web site: gomerch.com. It also describes the choices available to you regarding our use of your personal information and how you can access and update this information.

TRUSTe

If you have questions or concerns regarding this policy, you should first contact us at Privacy@GoMerch.com. If you do not receive acknowledgment of your inquiry, or if your inquiry has not been satisfactorily addressed, you should then contact TRUSTe. TRUSTe will then serve as a liaison with the Web site to resolve your concerns.

Collection and Use | Information Sharing | Tracking Technologies | Security | Additional Info | Contact Info Collection and Use of Personal Information

We collect the following personal information from you

* Contact Information such as name, email address, mailing address, phone number  
* Billing Information such as credit card number, and billing address  
* Unique Identifiers such as user name, account number, password  
* Preferences Information such as product wish lists, order history, marketing preferences

As is true of most Web sites, we automatically gather information about your computer such as your IP address, browser type, referring/exit pages, and operating system.

We use this information to

* Fulfill your order  
* Send you an order confirmation  
* Send you requested product or service information  
* Send product updates or warranty information  
* Respond to customer service requests  
* Administer your account  
* Send you a newsletter  
* Send you marketing communications  
* Respond to your questions and concerns  
* Improve our Web site and marketing efforts  
* Conduct research and analysis

Choice/Opt-Out

You may choose to stop receiving our newsletter or marketing emails by following the unsubscribe instructions included in these emails or you can contact us at Privacy@GoMerch.com.

Information Obtained from Third Parties

We obtain address information about you from third party sources, such as the US Postal Service, to verify your address so we can properly ship your order to you and to prevent fraud.

Information Sharing

We will share your personal information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this privacy statement. We do not sell your personal information to third parties.

We may provide your personal information to companies that provide services to help us with our business activities such as shipping your order or offering customer service. These companies are authorized to use your personal information only as necessary to provide these services to us.

We may also disclose your personal information

* as required by law such as to comply with a subpoena, or similar legal process  
* when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request,  
* if GoMerch is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Web site of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information,  
* to any other third party with your prior consent to do so.

Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies

We may use cookies, for example, to keep track of your preferences and profile information. Cookies are also used to collect general usage and volume statistical information that does not include personal information.

Our Web pages contain electronic images known as Web beacons (sometimes called single-pixel gifs) and are used along with cookies to compile aggregated statistics to analyze how our site is used and may be used in some of our emails to let us know which emails and links have been opened by recipients. This allows us to gauge the effectiveness of our customer communications and marketing campaigns. Our Web pages may also contain electronic images known as Web beacons (sometimes called single-pixel gifs) that are set by our third party partners. Web beacons are used along with cookies enabling our partners to compile aggregated statistics to analyze how our site is used.

Links to Other Web Sites

Our Site includes links to other Web sites whose privacy practices may differ from those of GoMerch. If you submit personal information to any of those sites, your information is governed by their privacy statements. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy statement of any Web site you visit.

Security

The security of your personal information is important to us. When you enter sensitive information (such as credit card number) on our order forms, we encrypt the transmission of that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL).

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can contact us at Privacy@GoMerch.com

Additional Policy Information

Our Web site includes Widgets, which are interactive mini-programs that run on our site to provide specific services from another company (e.g. displaying the news, opinions, music, etc). Personal information, such as your email address, may be collected through the Widget. Cookies may also be set by the Widget to enable it to function properly. Information collected by this Widget is governed by the privacy policy of the company that created it.

Our Web site offers publicly accessible blogs or community forums. You should be aware that any information you provide in these areas may be read, collected, and used by others who access them.

Correcting and Updating Your Personal Information

To review and update your personal information to ensure it is accurate, contact us at Privacy@GoMerch.com.

Notification of Privacy Statement Changes

We may update this privacy statement to reflect changes to our information practices. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on this Site prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.

Contact Information

You can contact us about this privacy statement by writing or email us at the address below:  
GoMerch  
6400 Canoga Ave, Suite 360  
Woodland Hills, CA 91367  
Email: [mailroom@GoMerch.com](mailto:mailroom@gomerch.com)  
Phone: 818-882-3277
